<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on JMNofziger</title>
    <link>https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on JMNofziger</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 13:42:55 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Models and Deployment</title>
      <link>https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/post/django-models-and-deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 13:42:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/post/django-models-and-deploy/</guid>
      <description>Finally had some free time to come back to my prepared Django environment and mess around with a starter project. You can follow the same walkthrough I did. I&amp;rsquo;ll just highlight some of the interesting things learned.
 Object Models and Django  Objects - a way to describe real things in code with properties and actions object properties == property of a thing methods == actions of a thing Applying object model to Django blog posts properties: title, text, author, created_date, published_date methods: publish  Applications and Django  Create separate apps within prject to keep things organized Create app with manage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Django Env Setup</title>
      <link>https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/post/initial-django-env/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 18:12:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/post/initial-django-env/</guid>
      <description>Django is a web framework that runs on python. Now that I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten well acquainted with the python syntax exploring Django has become much more intriguing. In this post I work through the DjangoGirls intro to Django tutorial which was presented in Seattle in April 2017. One of my classmates attended (Margarita) and passed on the tutorial to me. You can find the walkthrough here: https://tutorial.djangogirls.org/en/
In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll just summarize the setup through the point at which Django serves its default project page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Hugo To Subdirectory</title>
      <link>https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/post/deploying-hugo-to-subdirectory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 12:39:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmnofziger.github.io/journal/post/deploying-hugo-to-subdirectory/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been exploring Hugo for a bit and decided that I&amp;rsquo;d like to deploy my fresh blog site to the /blog/ subdirectory of my https://jmnofziger.github.io base url. However, my attempts to do that locally resulted in resources not being linked correctly. CSS stylesheets couldn&amp;rsquo;t be found, JS scripts couldn&amp;rsquo;t be found; all my resources were return 404. An inspection with the browser console showed that resource URL&amp;rsquo;s weren&amp;rsquo;t being updated to reflect https://jmnofziger.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>